<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="abc_action_bar_home_description">Navigate home</string>
    <string name="abc_action_bar_home_description_format">%1$s, %2$s</string>
    <string name="abc_action_bar_home_subtitle_description_format">%1$s, %2$s, %3$s</string>
    <string name="abc_action_bar_up_description">Navigate up</string>
    <string name="abc_action_menu_overflow_description">More options</string>
    <string name="abc_action_mode_done">Done</string>
    <string name="abc_activity_chooser_view_see_all">See all</string>
    <string name="abc_activitychooserview_choose_application">Choose an app</string>
    <string name="abc_capital_off">OFF</string>
    <string name="abc_capital_on">ON</string>
    <string name="abc_search_hint">Search…</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_clear">Clear query</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_query">Search query</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_search">Search</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_submit">Submit query</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_voice">Voice search</string>
    <string name="abc_shareactionprovider_share_with">Share with</string>
    <string name="abc_shareactionprovider_share_with_application">Share with %s</string>
    <string name="abc_toolbar_collapse_description">Collapse</string>
    <string name="status_bar_notification_info_overflow">999+</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="app_name">Repackaging Lab</string>
    <string name="appbar_scrolling_view_behavior">android.support.design.widget.AppBarLayout$ScrollingViewBehavior</string>
    <string name="character_counter_pattern">%1$d / %2$d</string>
    <string name="labDescriptionText1">Repackaging attack is a very common type of attacks on Android devices. In such an attack, attackers modify a popular app downloaded from app markets, reverse engineer the app, add some malicious payloads, and then upload the modified app to app markets. Users can be easily fooled, because it is hard to notice the difference between the modified app and the original app. Once the modified apps are installed, the malicious code inside can conduct attacks, usually in the background. For example, in March 2011, it was found that DroidDream Trojan had been embedded into more than 50 apps in Android official market and had infected many users. DroidDream Trojan exploits vulnerabilities in Android to gain the root access on the device.</string>
    <string name="labDescriptionText2">The learning objective of this lab is for students to gain a first-hand experience in Android repackaging attack, so they can better understand this particular risk associated with Android systems, and be more cautious when downloading apps to their devices, especially from those untrusted third-party markets. In this lab, students will be asked to conduct a simple repackage attack on a selected app, and demonstrate the attack only on our provided Android VM.</string>
    <string name="labDescriptionText3">STUDENTS SHOULD BE WARNED NOT TO SUBMIT THEIR REPACKAGED APPS TO ANY MARKET, OR THEY WILL FACE LEGAL CONSEQUENCE. NOR SHOULD THEY RUN THE ATTACK ON THEIR OWN ANDROID DEVICES, AS THAT MAY CAUSE REAL DAMAGES.</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="title_activity_lab">LabActivity</string>
</resources>
